[{"answer": "This was a support group for men with testicular cancer.  The big moosie slobbering all over me was my friend", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Yes.  We're men.  Men is what we are", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Telling me off.  Is it going as well as you hoped... ? ", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Go ahead.  I'll expose you", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I want that", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "So far, you have four and I only have two", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I guess so", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "All gone", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "The things you own, they end up owning you", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Do what you like", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Why don't you cut the shit and ask if you can stay at my place", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Is it a problem for you to ask", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Is it", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Call what off", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Call what off", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "What fight", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "The fight", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "This fight, pussy", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Okay", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Yes, I promise", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Promise you won't", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Promise", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Yes, I promise", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I said I promise", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "It isn't... ", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "We don't... ", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "There", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Here", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "A veterinarian", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Yeah ... animals and ", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Should I ", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "What do you want to know about Project Mayhem", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I don't know!  Nothing", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I would feel nothing about my life? Is that what you want to hear?", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "When", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "This conversation..", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "... is over", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "... A person", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Why would you ask if it's a guy or a girl?", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "But, this is Project Mayhem", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "But, in Project Mayhem, we have no names", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "... You know me", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Yes... it's a test", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Will you just answer me, for my friend?", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "We did make love", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "You broke your promise.  You talked to her about me", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Why did you do that", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Answer me, my friend", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "I don't know!  Tell me", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "What... ", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "What are you talking about... ", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "The house is rented in your name", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Night jobs", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Night jobs", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "What about my friend", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "Sixty seconds, then I'm out of here", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "I've done you enough favors", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "I can't let you..", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "I'm going to..", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "my friend was a grown man.  In any great struggle, there will be casualties. Wouldn't that be implicit in the name?  Project", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "You want out", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Ask me nicely", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "Defuse the bomb", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "No more running off without you. From here on out, we do it together", "docId": "Fight-Club.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "I'm doing this for us", "qsentId": 66}]